Visit turkision.com for more!
Come on then!
The Eternal!
A grand migration is coming from the steppe...
...it's hard to carry the burden for the helpless.
The young lead the way, the old come later.
Make way! A hennaed sheep is coming on shoulders!
Come on then!
Let's see who's the fastest in the tribe!
In the name of Allah!
Come on!
Come on Alps!
Aykurt!
Come on, my Shahzade!
Come on Alps!
Come on, come on!
Turahan, hang on!
Be careful!
Come on
I let you win because you have a wedding, brother.
Or else, I'd win.
Yes sure!
My children...
Of people!
From the horse, a stallion...
...from the sheep, a ram, from the camel...
..a bullock will be sacrificed
Now spread the news to all our cities!
Food will be distributed for
forty days and forty nights!
May Allah bless you, my Bey!
May Allah bless you too.
What happened, Alaeddin?
Why are you standing there, my son?
Don't worry. Soon, we will
organize your wedding as well.
We will take Gonca for you, my son.
Then...
...then you will defeat your brother in the game.
I hope so my Bey.
May my Allah show us those days.
Aameen.
So...
If those fitna causers and
dastards do not stop us...
...we will see those days with Allah's permission.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
Welcome, father.
Isn't my mother here?
You know how we left this place, Mehmed.
She didn't want to come
back and see Osman's Hatuns.
They will take the dowries to Sinop.
You tell me.
Where is that traitor, your sister?
I put her in the caged tent, father.
To stop her from making a mistake and running away.
Gonca..
Go.
My Alaeddin..
I am determined for this love.
I'll keep my word.
Will you keep yours too?
Alaeddin
Father!
Father, thanks to Allah! You came!
Father, thanks to Allah! You..
Who are you to..
...disregard my orders and do what you want?
Gonca...
Is this the girl I raised?
Father, I..
While I was struggling for
the well-being of the state...
...worrying about our future...
...you went and fell in love
with my enemy's son, huh?
My daughter...
...does what is necessary...
...for the well-being of the state.
-She will marry Candaroglu Ahmet.
-Enough, father!
I can think clearly!
I love Alaeddin Bey.
No matter what..
...I will die, but I will never marry someone else!
-Shut up!
You will marry Candaroglu Ahmet.
Soon, your fiance will be here.
Go and make yourself presentable.
You used to get mad at my mother.
But power has blinded you, father.
Father...
I don't know you anymore..
It's you who is blind to the truth.
But...
But I know how to open your blind eyes.
If you make a mistake,
If you disgrace me
...I swear...
...I will burn both you and Alaaddin.
Get out of my sight!
The biggest obstacle against us...
...is the alliance between
Candaroglu and Germiyanoglu.
They're both setting up games
and joining the wedding, my Bey.
They know you won't accept gifts
but only demand loyalty from the beys.
Yes, they do. They'll attempt to divert the beys.
-They'll come to show off.
-Yakup Bey...
...always does things secretly, my Bey.
Still, we'll try to break their alliance
without shedding the brother's blood.
Continue the preparations for Mekece, though.
No matter what they do, we won't stop conquering.
My Bey!
We got a message.
They located Konur. Konur...
...is going to pay for the gold that he stole.
-Orhan.
-My Bey.
You stay in the tribe. There'll be
people who come to the wedding.
-Be cautious.
-As you order, my Bey.
-Aladdin, you go to the frontier market.
-My Bey.
Welcome Yakup Bey there. And smell the air.
-Get some information.
-As you order, my Bey.
Konur's fate won't be different from a criminal.
-Cerkutay.
-My Bey.
Tell the alps...
If anyone steps back from fighting,
I will sign their death warrants.
Come on.
Allah has given me whatever I wanted from Him.
A smart husband and a
son who listens to his mother.
Tell me, boy. Did you accomplish your duty?
I located Konur Bey, one of Osman Bey's alps.
Good boy.
Konur will be the key of my
sovereignty in the frontiers.
I will hold him in my hands first.
See? Your father intends to crush
the foreign lands before stepping on it.
We'll do the same again, mother.
I hear your words again...
...and ignore what I heard
about Gonca Hatun and Alaaddin.
You still see this matter as a duty.
Gonca Hatun is going to be your wife!
Our beylic's honor is your honor.
Fathers agreed and there will be a marriage.
You say I shouldn't show
mercy if Alaaddin crosses the line.
-You shouldn't.
-I won't, mother.
I won't.
Are you picking up the ripe fruits, husband?
I won't be bothered to
bend if it's valuable, hatun.
What matters to me is the
future of Candaroglu family.
This marriage...
...will make us much more powerful than before.
-I know, father.
-You know.
You know but you should also know this.
You father takes measures and plans his every move.
If you show weakness it will be pity for us.
If this marriage doesn't happen
...there will be no Germiyan or Candar.
All of us will be subject to Ottomans.
-May Allah forbid that.
-Now...
Everyone should do their own duties.
You go to the frontier market
and please Yakup Bey's mind...
..and Gonca Hatun's heart.
I'll take care of this matter
and join you afterwards.
-Come back victorious, my Bey.
-Come on.
Who are they, my Bey?
-I have never seen them before.
-They are former Seljukian soldiers.
Traitors. They loot the caravans in the frontiers.
They steal gold.
Alps, let's go.
-We're under attack.
-Who are those people coming?
We'll see.
-My Bey, some people are coming.
-Come on, Cerkutay.
Find Konur for me.
-Is that clear?
-As you order, my Bey.
Konur...
It's time for you to pay.
Run and save your life, Konur.
If Osman Bey catches you, he won't let you live.
You must go beyond me first to take Konur!
-Who are you?
-Come on, attack!
Konur, where are you going?
Where do you think you are going?
I've seen many battles and enemies
but never seen Osman Bey so angry.
-Come on, brothers!
-There will be a blood bath after this.
-Konur Bey will be wasted.
-Come on, come on.
Konur!
Where are you going? Where
do you think you are going?
Konur... Cerkutay!
-My Bey.
Trails go this way. You go that way!
Look at me! Bring Konur to me!
Whoever steps back from fighting
will pay a heavy price for this!
-Bring Konur to me! Come on!
-Come on!
If we can't find Konur
..our Bey will bury us here
with this anger, brothers.
Right.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
I want no mistakes, Gonca.
Act worthy of your family.
-Welcome, Melike Hatun.
-Thank you, Yakup Bey.
-Ahmed Bey.
-Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
-Where is Ibrahim Bey?
-My father Ibrahim Bey is on his way.
He will come to Kayi Tribe when his work is done.
Alright then.
My girl Gonca.
They said you were beautiful, however,
I did not expect it to be this much.
Praise be, you are very beautiful.
It was our destiny to meet today.
-Welcome, Melike Hatun.
-Thank you, my daughter.
I can say that you are my daughter now as well.
I've heard your fame. You
were running from battle to battle.
They say you are acting
a little independent as well.
-You know everything about me, is that right?
-What can I say.
I am getting a bride to the
mighty Candaroglu, my girl.
You came from afar.
Here, let us go to our tent.
Please, this way.
Wedding caravan is coming!
-Welcome, Gunduz Bey.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
-Welcome, Gunduz Bey.
-Thank you.
-Welcome, my daughter.
-Thank you, mother Malhun.
Congratulations, my daughter.
I hope you always stand behind
each other's back.
-I hope so.
My daughter, come here.
Today, these seeds will fall upon the earth.
When they grow and spread..
..may your house also grow and spread,
if Allah permits.
-I hope you always trust each other
-I hope so.
Orhan, my son.
This soil is Horasan soil.
Today, the place of your tent will be decided.
Spread this soil to the
place where your tent will be.
So that..
..your children may inherit..
..the glorious cause you
inherited from your father.
Ameen, Gunduz Bey.
-You can trust me with this.
-Praise be, praise be.
I can't see Osman Bey. Where is he?
Our Bey has went to get rid of one of our troubles.
-He will come back soon, if Allah permits.
-What is it Orhan Bey?
-We could've helped.
-Our Bey didn't think it was necessary.
It is about Konur. He did wrong to us.
-Come on, let us talk at the tent.
-Come, my daughter.
Konur!
If you take another step,
I will kill you before you talk!
Konur. How could you do this to me?
Get up
Get up.
Get up!
At least stand tall when you are dying!
Look at me!
Look!
Look at me.
I banished you instead when
your punishment was death.
I banished you.
And what did you do?
Look at me. You stabbed me from the back.
You stabbed me from the back.
Haven't you ate my food and drink from my water?
Haven't you!
Answer me. Answer me!
I only do what I know, my Bey.
Come here. Is this what I taught you?
Did I teach you infamy! Is
this what you are saying?
The wound you opened still stays.
I forgave you despite all you
did. I've known you as family.
I put you at the head of my
army. And what did you do?
What did you do to me? Now..
-..you will tell me why you betrayed me.
-I do everything for holy war.
I never went off my path.
-By stealing State's gold?
-I only followed this path for holy war.
-This is my way.
-Still talking about holy war.
Get up! He still says holy war!
The right of oppressed is the State's gold!
Who gave you this authority? Who?
-Tell me, who?
-Count those coins..
..as payment for the lands, my Bey. I
had sword's right for those lands as well.
I will spend those gold and
my life for the sake of holy war.
Is that so.
I gave you those lands.
And I will take them from you.
Your life is in my hands as well.
I will not let you have it as well.
These cloths..
..has been brought from India
and Damascus for you only.
However, it seems you didn't like them.
I didn't, Ahmed Bey.
If you are looking to impress a
woman with couple of clothing..
..you can wander this marketplace.
We are engaged now.
I am not searching for anyone
other than you, Gonca Hatun.
However, I knew I would get this
response, you didn't surprise me.
For you to decorate your beauty.
You do not want this marriage. I know that.
However, this marriage..
..is a duty for both of us now.
Who knows, maybe we can know..
..each other-
Gonca?
Alaeddin.
It seems Osman Bey sent him to escort.
Come on!
Yakup Bey. Melike Hatun.
I brought salutations from my father. Welcome.
All precautions are taken on the roads.
We will escort you.
Fitnat. Finish your business with Gonca.
We will be on the road afterall.
Your father thinks of everything.
He sends you to us. Tell me..
..how can he let Imren have..
..my lands, my marketplace!
Mehmed Bey must've told you everything, Yakup Bey.
We set up a trap to defeat Imren.
We killed Imren and we took back the marketplace.
It is not about giving or taking, Alaeddin Bey.
It is about setting up traps on Yakup Bey's land..
..without his knowledge.
It seems you don't know how this works, Ahmed Bey.
We do not do anything for our personal gain.
-Against infidels- -You are right, Alaeddin.
However, you did this without
telling me, you didn't trust us.
There was a traitor inside, Mehmed.
If there wasn't any, why wouldn't we trust you?
Besides, its not like..
..you will do any business
and unite behind our back.
We are soldiers of the same cause.
Isn't that right, Yakup Bey?
I've kept a snake by my side for all these years.
I entrusted my family to you,
I entrusted everything to you.
I entrusted my army to you.
But you stabbed me in the back.
Now,
-tell me where the gold is.
-I did not betray you.
Either let me go and I'll become a
martyr and I will be killed by you now.
Both is an honor for me.
-This is my last word.
-Wrong move
is the killer of the right path.
You will be punished for what you did.
Protect the Bey!
Who are these men?
Osman, I'm here to drink blood
I'm here to shed blood!
-We're coming my Bey.
-Come on, brothers!
Either come with me or die by Osman's hands.
My Bey, Konur ran away
and they set the horses free.
Konur! Where will you run?
My Bey! Who are they? What
do they have to do with Konur?
Just a jackal collaborating with Konur.
We will kill them all. Come on.
So you were the spy, is that so?
How could you not tell me about it?
My Bey! They had my child and my Hatun.
I had no other choice, my Bey. Forgive me, my Bey.
Kanyumaz!
-It's not a big deal, Mehmed.
Kanyumaz sold Osman out.
-He hurt him, not us.
-Osman Bey.
He will kill me if he finds out that
I was spying for Imren.
You are under my protection, Kanyumaz.
Yes, my Sultan.
-Osman Bey,
can't do anything to you.
From now on, Osman will have even more troubles.
What are you going to do, father?
I formed an alliance with the Lord of Mekece.
Our trade is going well.
When the time comes, we will attack
we will take the castle, and when we have Mekece
Bursa and Iznik will be ours as well.
Osman's biggest dream
is to have Bursa and Iznik.
Osman will never be able to get what he wants.
We will conquer them.
That's why we made an alliance with Candaroglus.
Osman won't let it happen,
father. He will confront us.
Neither Osman
nor Alaeddin, I will not let any of them
break this union and stop us.
From now on, we will not show
mercy to those who stand against us.
Osman, Alaeddin, Orhan..
Whoever it is,
we will crush him.
No, it's nowhere to be found.
What am I going to say to my Bey?
He's coming. Aykurt.
-Baysungur, did you find the gold?
-My Bey.
-Gold...
-Where's the gold?
-There's no gold, my Bey.
-What do you mean?
Konur raids the caravans and does all he wants.
What are my alps doing?
Tell me, what are you doing?
Look at me, Baysungur. Aykurt!
-You will find the gold and Konur.
-Yes, my Bey.
Got it?
Just like you handed him over
you will find him back.
Yes, my Bey.
Back to work, everyone.
-My Bey.
No one will come after me.
-My Bey...
Cerkutay, you too.
Alps, be careful.
Not only us, this fire
can burn even a steel sword.
I know the taste of steel and blood very well.
What are you going to do? Will you kill me?
Tell me, how did you find me and who are you?
I saved you, Konur.
Ibrahim Bey.
How did you find me?
I heard that Osman Bey exiled you.
Husrev is serving me, and you had a life to life.
Tell me, why did you steal Osman Bey's gold?
Western cities heard about it.
-Tell me about the truth behind it.
-If courage is needed for the battle
the gold is needed as well,
otherwise no one will stand behind you.
You're saying battle.
If you're choosing battle, stand behind me.
Don't think that it would be inappropriate.
I'll solve your problem with Osman Bey
and settle the issue.
You're saying battle.
What is your target, Ibrahim Bey?
Konur, hear me out.
We have saved your life but are you questioning us?
Konur's purpose in life is battle
of course he would question.
My goal is the whole north of Byzantium,
then Lznik, Bursa.
It is Osman Bey's target. If
you're not from the same pack
two wolves cannot hunt in the same mountain.
It does not matter who carries the banner.
Think about it very well and make up your mind.
We will make Orhan Bey's wedding,
we will take Gonca bride and go back to Sinop.
You have time until then.
Alright Ibrahim Bey.
May Allah protect you.
Distribute this piece to my brothers.
About you...
Turk.
Bite me if you want to bite.
Don't just show your teeth.
Or I'll pull your teeth out.
If I wanted to kill you
I had already ripped your neck off with my teeth.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
No, my Shahzade. Gonca
Hatun is nowhere to be found.
Where are you, Gonca?
Guice, where is Gonca?
They put her in the caged tent when
she said she won't marry Candaroglu.
-She will not take her to the wedding.
-How could Yakup Bey let this happen?
Yakup Bey was very angry with Gonca Hatun.
They will send Gonca Hatun to
Sinop after the wedding tomorrow.
Tell her that Alaeddin will save
you no matter what happens.
Come on.
Yakup Bey, Yakup Bey.
My Shahzade. Yakup Bey
and others are ready to set out.
Come on.
I have nowhere to go but you.
I heard that you're all alone now.
You lost your ma'am Olivia.
And you know Gonca very well.
Then tell me about Gonca and Alaeddin.
Gonca Hatun and Alaeddin
Bey love each other very much.
Everyone in the Frontiers knows this.
Ertugrul Ghazi...
My glorious father...
We conquered many castles and
ended a crusade before it even started.
We said... "Sure..
...now Turks are becoming a union. The
one who sees gaza stands by our side."
But...
But those who we called our brothers...
...those who we called our
brothers fell into carelessness.
They set a trap on our way.
Now., now we are alone like you.
Now there are a few of us. But we will get crowded.
Your grandson Orhan is getting married today.
Then Alaeddin...
Right... Right.
We don't need...
...we don't need anyone to support us.
Our essence and our end are this land.
But our struggle is still on
this land, isn't it, Osman Bey?
Our struggle is against the
unbelievers. Surely, we know.
We know, but those who
stand behind us with a dagger...
...and bow their heads to pray with us...
That...
That tightens our hearts.
The Hadith says...
..."Muslims are like the stones of a
building, each one supporting the other.'
If the stones are separated,
the building collapses.
That's why our Prophet (PBUH) said
"Don't hold grudges against each other...
...don't envy each other, don't
turn your backs on each other...
...O servants of Allah, be brothers/'.
Why does he warn us?
Because shaytaan tries to deceive
the one on the right path the most.
Muslims desire as well.
Your desires can deceive you.
It holds a grudge, it envies.
Now, as your da'wah grows, as you get stronger...
...those around you are tested...
...with their ambitions and envy.
And you are tested with pride and justice.
Now, if you are fair like our Prophet...
...if you show tolerance,
surely you will pass the test.
Those brothers who see the justice in you...
...will leave their grudge overcome their envy...
...wake up from the sleep of carelessness
and pass their tests, if Allah permits.
But...
...what about those who cannot wake
up from the sleep of carelessness?
If they persist in committing a sin...
...they will sow seeds of disbelief
in their hearts, may Allah forbid.
I know... I know.
Your way is difficult. May my Allah help you.
May He let you be victorious
against all your enemies
the ones you can see
and cannot see, I hope.
Aameen. Aameen, the Sultan of
words, Yunus Emre. Thank you.
Gonca Hatun... I heard such things that...
...it was Kanyumaz who
informed Imren about Osman Bey.
What are you saying, Guice?
What did my father say to this?
-He didn't say anything!
He forgave him by saying it only hurt Osman.
He united with Candaroglu to take Bursa and Iznik.
They made an alliance with Mekece Lord.
They are saying that they can even
walk over Osman Bey for this path.
They are saying that they will
kill whoever stands in their way.
He was defeated by Osman Bey when he left...
...he is blinded by his ambition.
No... My father is going to
make a big mistake, Guice.
-What are you going to do, my Hatun?
-There is only one thing I can do now.
You will bring me a piece of paper and a pen.
I will send a letter to Alaeddin Bey. Go.
Alaeddin Bey gave it to me. He
said he would not leave you here.
I am loyal to my oath, Scholar.
No matter what, I won't go back.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you, I appreciate it.
-Thanks
-May your family grow!
Oh Praise be!
Thank you Gunduz Bey.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
It fell right on target, brother.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Prase be! Praise be!
May their family be blessed.
Praise be! Praise be!
Sisters, give me the water.
May it be blessed! -Aameen!
Aameen!
Alps! Start building the tent!
It'll be ready by evening.
May my Allah let you see the
tent of your children, I hope.
Aameen.
-May you live in peace.
-Aameen.
You all know. For the future of our nation,
...Elcim Hatun and I are getting
married. For the same cause.
-And we will raise our children with Allah's will.
-If Allah permits.
Malhun, are you alright?
I have a killing ache here.
And it's getting stronger.
-Oh no. Are you serious?
-Look.
It hurts too much.
We should make Aladdin check this.
-Alright. Alright.
-Let's go.
-Welcome, my Bey!
-Osman Bey, welcome!
Is there a problem, Osman Bey? Seeing
the alps coming back early, we got worried.
I went to tell my father Ertugrul Ghazi
about the wedding of his grandson.
But it's not about the wedding.
-Konur?
-Yes, Konur.
He'll get both himself and us ruined.
He's attempting recruit men
for himself with Olcaytu's gold.
-Whatever.
-My Bey.
-I hope the wedding won't be delayed.
-No, don't worry.
I dispersed the looters around him.
He can't regain his strength easily.
Everybody for himself, Osman Bey.
I hope he'll make up for his mistake.
I hope so, I hope so.
I've been unfair to you.
What we have gone through...
I blamed you without listening.
I drew a dagger against you.
I want to apologize.
Yes. We have gone through a lot.
But, it wasn't our fault.
As I get to know you better,
my conscience chokes me.
Release your conscience from this suffering.
-You couldn't have known.
-I'm sorry.
For everything.
Don't be. For the future of thousands of people,
...you had to do it.
We had to.
I'm waiting for a ship. When it
arrives, I'll go to Constantinople.
Otherwise, I would never
be here on your wedding day.
It seems you made up your mind.
May you have a safe journey.
Give me your blessings
in this world and the doomsday.
I do.
Welcome to our wedding.
Welcome!
-Thank you.
-Welcome, Melike Hatun.
-Welcome.
Is this your first time in the frontiers?
Thank you. Yes. It's my first.
We came to take the new bride
Gonca and also for the wedding.
Osman Bey, it's an honor...
...for me to meet a valiant Turkish Bey like you.
I hope your wedding will bring the good.
-I hope so, I hope so.
-I hope so.
I was expecting to find you..
...in the palace in Yenisehir.
But you said you'd have the wedding in the tribe.
Well... I wanted your feet...
...to touch the ground, Ibrahim Bey.
Thanks for welcoming, Osman Bey.
But the situation doesn't seem well to me.
You used the frontier market to repel Crusaders.
If you had failed
...the price would have been very heavy.
I carry the rock with my own hands only.
I do that...
...so nobody will doubt
whether I can shoulder it or not.
Right, Ibrahim Bey?
Ha?
While Crusaders were preparing to attack us,
...where were you?
Tell me. Where were you?
If we hadn't finished Crusade before
it even started, then all the Turks...
..would have suffered from it.
Whatever.
I don't expect gratitude from anyone.
But if someone attempts to
resist while we fight Crusaders,
...we will never let that happen!
Everyone should know that.
Who is even resisting you?
The enemy stopped because we stopped them together.
Didn't you have...
...the support of Germiyan in your every victory?
Didn't my son Mehmed Bey stand behind you?
He shouldn't have stood beside me, not behind me.
Yakup Bey.
Now we're standing beside you, Osman Bey.
We're in the wedding of your son Orhan Bey.
We shouldn't dwell on the matter on this happy day.
If Allah permits, we will have
wedding and fights together.
Alright then.
So be it. It's better than you standing against me.
We'll have many more happy
days. Let me tell you my target then.
Bursa and Iznik!
Oh, Osman Bey. Oh... Be patient.
Your alps, horses and you should rest first.
No. Alps fall on the ground and horses die.
And a bey leaves his chair to his son.
But we never rest.
As they say...
Our dreams are longer than our lives.
Yes.
Well, Beys... Your dream is our dream.
It's alright. But...
Both Germiyan and Candar
have trade with Bursa and Iznik.
This move of yours...
...won't be beneficial to us.
We should think thoroughly then.
Right, Ibrahim Bey?
Should we be Beys who care about their people...
...or be merchants to deal with trade?
Neither trade nor beylic, Osman Bey!
As you said
...we should give our service to our people.
That's why Yakup Bey and I are
making our children get married.
For more powerful armies.
Alright then. Let's get to the tent...
..and discuss it.
Let us see who will be happy..
..about the conquest of Bursa and Iznik..
..and who will be upset.
Let us go.
Melike Hatun. Let us go to the arbour.
Alaeddin, what is it, brother? You seem upset.
They locked Gonca in the caged tent.
Are there any news from Konur?
I've heard from Osman's men.
-He escaped.
-Good.
Then, he will come here.
Have you lost your mind, Boran? Shut it!
I haven't lost it, but you will.
Do not worry.
My Osman Bey will show you.
Shut him up!
I will not let you live this time, Boran.
Konur is the reason why you are alive.
You will not let me you say? That will be right.
Do not hold back! Come!
Will you do it by yourself?
So you will do it by yourself.
Come, Konur Bey. This will be settled today.
Come.
We thought you would arrange
your wedding at the palace.
However, you arranged it at the tribe.
One should not forget where
they came from, Melike Hatun.
As both the tribe and the palace is ours.
They are.
We will arrange our son Ahmed and our
daughter Gonca's wedding at the palace.
-You must've heard about it, Bala Hatun.
-Yes, we've heard it.
May everything come out good in the end.
We were hoping to see Saadet
Hatun. Why didn't she come?
Saadet brought the dowery to Sinop.
As you know, there are a lot of work
to be done, wedding is getting closer.
You can see Saadet at Sinop.
Let us see when the time comes, Melike Hatun.
Those times are very close, Malhun Hatun.
You are uniting two Kayis..
..and we are uniting two tribes.
No one will have the strength
to seperate this unity anymore.
Where is our girl Gonca, Melike Hatun?
You are talking about wedding and all.
However, your bride is not here.
Does she not want this marriage?
My daughter Gonca is a little ill. She
wouldn't leave me alone otherwise.
Orhan Bey is getting married.
It is your son's turn, Bala Hatun.
What was his name?
Alaeddin Ali.
These things are bound to fate, Melike Hatun.
My Alaeddin might get married before we know it.
-If Allah permits, Bala.
-If Allah permits.
If Allah permits
I do not understand, brother. How
can a father put his daughter in a cell?
They know Gonca won't stand
still. However, do not worry, brother.
-We will not leave Gonca there.
-Of course we will not.
She feels alone now as she got
backstabbed by her most trusted.
I should be with her now.
You will be.
A little patience, you will be.
If Allah permits, brother.
Mehmed. Heartless Mehmed.
You stood against your
sister instead of being with her.
Alaeddin, they must not
know we know where Gonca is.
Stay calm, brother.
You don't leave the training
grounds even at the wedding day.
These Kayis are just like that, Ahmed Bey.
What is it, Alaeddin Bey? You seem quite angry?
No. That is just what you think, Mehmed Bey.
We couldn't meet properly at marketplace,
Alaeddin Bey, I've heard about your name.
You are a student of knowledge. You went to school.
So, what are you doing at the training grounds?
However, we never heard about your name, Ahmed Bey.
-What is your virtue?
-Didn't you hear it?
He is engaged to Gonca. Who
else would be better for her.
By the way, his sword is sharp..
..and his wrist in unmatched.
Yes.
You work with pencils I work with swords.
Is that so, Ahmed Bey?
You didn't hear about him enough.
Alaeddin does not only work
with pencils. He is skilled at arms..
..as much as he is skilled with pencils.
If you want to see for
yourself, here is the valiant.
-And here is the field.
-Alright then.
Let us see your skills, Alaeddin Bey.
Come on, brother.
You will have wedding soon as well.
Soon, if Allah permits. We will go to Sinop..
..and arrange the wedding at Ibrahim Bey's land.
Let us invite you while we are here, Gunduz Bey.
Of course, we shall come.
Of course we will come.
We will not leave you alone..
..in this glorious day.
However..
..we want you at the field of war with us.
If you say you don't want to join...
...so be it.
However, know this.
We will conquer Bursa and Iznik.
Do not stand against us.
Do not even think about it.
Everyone..
..everyone will know their hunting grounds.
Your honesty has...
...made me really happy, Osman Bey.
Now you're talking about a hunting ground...
What about the prey? Say this as well.
Bursa and Iznik are not preys for us.
Those are the goats that have strayed...
..from our flock to yours.
We milk them.
We trade with them.
We profit from them.
The prey is not determined by shepherds...
...only by wolves.
We call Bursa and Iznik...
...our prey. How will this happen?
If we say we'll set out tomorrow..
...will you stand against us?
If necessary yes, Osman Bey.
You got used to making decisions alone...
...just because we withdrew to Kutahya once.
From now on, moves will
be made together as a unity.
Good then. We will either go there together...
...or I will walk over you, know that!
Because your intention is not trading.
Why do you say that, Osman Bey?
Tell us then, what
is our intention?
Your intention is
to take these cities.
Your intention is to block our
path, to strike a blow against us.
Ever since my father took Sogut
our arrow has always been...
...aimed at Bursa and Iznik. Know this.
We will take those cities.
Either with you or without you.
Make your decision.
While no one says a certain thing...
...you speak like an arrow, Osman Bey.
We always shoot our arrows at the infidels.
If it finds you...
...then you're in the wrong place.
This is not a matter to be
discussed between two weddings.
Let your wedding and our wedding happen...
...and when the time comes, we'll determine...
...our gaza and our trade.
If you want to speak with me...
...you'll find me only on the battlefield.
Safely.
Osman still magnifies himself even in
his tribe which looks like a sheepfold.
We need to open his eyes, Yakup Bey.
We will. We will.
He will know his place and his limits.
Tugay. Inform Olcay.
It's time. Now our swords will speak.
I explored the marketplace, my
Bey. The storekeepers stay at the inn.
When we kill storekeepers and burn their goods...
...Osman's trade will be over, right, Yakup Bey?
Yes. Right.
I think we should do it at night,
during the wedding ceremony, my Bey.
If we burn and destroy everything with a
sudden night raid, we'll get what we want.
You thought well Tugay.
And this will be useful for my co-in-law.
Making brothers enemies will let
us gain something today, my Bey.
What if it causes something bad the other day?
Our aim is to make Osman fall.
If he does not fall, he will
cause many other bad things.
Osman... Your end has come
Osman. Your end has come.
You are a guest at the frontiers. Go first.
Right... I am a guest. I will
take my fiancee and leave.
Aren't you too old now? Don't
you have someone you love?
I do. I do, but... Valiants keep their love secret.
Because it is valuable. We hide it in our hearts.
But apparently, your heart is empty.
Love is the toy of children!
I am doing my duty for my
Beylic! One can promise for once...
...and it is kept until the doomsday.
The word is our honour!
Praise be to my brother.
A word I will keep until I die.
Come at me.
Come at me, Ahmet Bey. Don't sit there.
Praise be, Alaeddin Bey. Praise be.
I don't count this one. In our
wedding with Gonca Hatun
-I'd like to do it one more time.
-What are you saying?
You will do it, Ahmed Bey.
After all, the beaten wrestler
is never satisfied with wrestling
But first, don't leave your sword on the ground.
Come on, brother.
Come on, Ahmed.
I know your wound, Alaeddin.
Your wound, will be my lover.
You are the one who lost this fight.
Alaeddin Bey.
-Guice? What happened?
-Gonca Hatun sent this to you.
Is Gonca all right?
I've come secretly I need to leave.
Gonca.
Mother.
-Something's going on.
-Turgut.
Watch Alaeddin, let me know if he leaves the tribe.
-Gonca will go to Sinop tomorrow.
-Let's go to my father.
-Come on, son.
-Come on.
Husrev.
Welcome, Konur. I've been waiting for you.
You will pay for your treason.
I chose my path, I did not betray.
Are you going to walk with them?
The path is right, Boran.
I took the marauders, but
my path is the same as Osman Bey.
It's been long since you left that path, Konur.
-Now you will pay for it all.
-You can take my life, Boran.
Listen to me carefully. Osman
Bey is in trouble. Help me.
-What trouble? What are you saying?
-Candaroglu Ibrahim Bey.
He saved me from Osman Bey
and he wanted to get me behind him.
Even Husrev is his man. They're up to something.
What are they after?
-What did you get into, Konur?
-We will find out, Boran.
He says he's here for Orhan
Bey's wedding, but I don't believe it.
They will plot against Osman Bey.
They will form an alliance with Yakup Bey.
They will unite and stab Osman Bey from his back.
There's only one way to find
out. We will be one of them.
You've seen what Gonca wrote. She says she
will send her to Sinop if we don't save her.
They are plotting against you. She
says they are plotting against you
and they will stop you for Bursa and Iznik.
-What are we going to do, Osman Bey?
-Their intention is to
stop the conquest of Bursa and Iznik.
They will use their trade as an
excuse. They will try to eliminate us.
Even the purpose of their wedding is to hurt us.
My Bey, father, Osman Bey.
Tell me whatever you want,
but for Allah's sake, don't say stop.
Son.
Their desires...
...lead their intentions.
So, you will go and take Gonca.
This will be the greatest strike against them.
Thank you, my Bey.
That's it. They crossed the
line, we will teach them a lesson.
Son. Go and bring my daughter-in-law.
-Now, my Bey?
-You're in such a hurry.
Just wait. Just wait.
During the wedding,
while everyone is in the
wedding, you will kidnap Gonca.
-Yes, my Bey. I will kidnap Gonca tonight.
-My brother.
-May it be mubarak.
-May it be mubarak, brother.
Let's get out.
-Son.
-Mother.
Take a look at your Malhun mother.
Her arm has been aching since morning.
-Mother, what happened?
-It's nothing important, son.
I feel a pain all of a sudden
but then it goes away.
No, it's not right.
We need to take a look. You know
that we should not ignore these things.
Let's have a look, son.
Look at the bride, henna in her hand
look at the bride, henna in her hand
don't say anything to her,
or she'll sulk and go away
congratulations for your henna,
may your tent be gorgeous,
congratulations for your henna
may your tent be gorgeous.
Look at the bride, henna in
her hand, look at the bride,
henna in her hand, don't say anything
to her, or she'll sulk and go away,
or she'll sulk away and
go, don't say anything to her
or she'll sulk and go away.
May it be mubarak, daughter.
May Allah bless you, daughter.
The way to exist in these blessed lands
is to be united, Beys.
And unity is established
behind the one who is stronger
and the one who will not put people
in a difficult situation for his whims.
You're right, Yakup Bey. For the
sake of these whims, many tribes
and many soldiers were ruined.
The state of Seljuks was a shield
for Turkmens and it was destroyed.
Now it is harder for the tribes.
if Allah permits, we will get rid of
the troubles with Osman Bey.
And I want to talk to you about this matter, Beys.
I know that Osman Bey called you to obey.
Do not obey Osman.
You were the one who told us to
unite. Why are you objecting now?
Because I don't want you to
be ruined for the sake of his goals, Halil Bey.
What should we do?
Obey me.
Only I have the power to
become a shield for the Turkmens.
My treasure is ten times larger than Osman's.
My alps are ten times more than Osman's.
-Kanyumaz.
Yes, my Sultan.
Alps.
If you bow down to Osman..
..you will break in misery.
If you stand beside me..
..you will get richer..
..and prevail with my gold.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Comeon, it is time for wedding.
I do not feel it.
It is stroke, mother.
It starts with your arm now, and Allah
forbid, it can spread to your body tomorrow.
You need to go to healing house at once.
Do not say anything to
anyone until the wedding is over.
Especially not to my Orhan. When the time comes..
..I will tell Osman Bey.
-Are you alright?
-I am alright.
Come on.
What we've heard was true, Ibrahim Bey.
Alaeddin and Gonca Hatun love each other.
-Everyone knew about it.
-It was apparent, mother.
We will make our move accordingly.
We will not make any moves, Hatun.
Ahmet!
You are marrying Gonca because of duty.
This is a State matter not a heart matter.
-Do not forget.
-I know that, father.
What if Osman's son tries to do something bad?
-What if he takes away the girl?
-Hatun!
Osman Bey..
..would not allow such madness.
All Turks would go against each other..
..and he knows this.
Right. He does not have the heart to do that.
If he does such a thing, we
would make him pay, mother.
Come on, let us leave. It is time for the wedding.
You came here from far away..
..to witness this glorious day of ours.
-May you prevail!
-Thank you, Osman Bey
May our Allah protect..
..our relation for eternity, if Allah permits.
-If Allah permits!
The marriage of my daughter
Elcim and my son Orhan..
..will unite Gunduz Bey's and our tribe.
I wish from my Allah..
..to have the same unity with other
Beyliks, and not only against infidels.
But against each other as well.
Of course, we want to be one..
..against the infidels. However..
..anyways.
Now, we can move onto the wedding of our children.
Come on, my children.
Elcim Hatun, daughter of Gunduz Bey.
Do you take Shahzade Orhan Bey son of Osman Bey..
..as your husband for five hundred dirham?
-I do.
Do you?
Shahzade Orhan Bey, son of Osman Bey.
Do you take Elcim Hatun, daughter of Gunduz Bey..
..as your wife for five hundred dirham?
I do.
-Holofira?
-Orhan?
-Do you?
-I do.
May Allah bless you both.
Oh Creator, the creator of the universe.
You have the grandness.
O, our Creator, protect our
children and our peers from harm.
-May You glorify this marriage.
-Ameen.
May You have us follow good
people who walk in the name of Allah.
-Ameen.
-Al Fatiha.
-May Allah bless it.
-Aameen.
Well... May Allah bless it.
-If Allah permits.
-ıf Allah permits, my Bey.
-May Allah give you...
...happiness both here and in afterlife.
Thank you. May Allah give you a long life.
Well, son..
May Allah never let taste the defeat.
Thank you, son. Thank you.
-Gunduz Bey.
-May Allah bless it.
I buried my son.
But Allah gave me another valiant son.
I trust you for my daughter
and trust my daughter for you.
Thank you, Gunduz Bey.
I will never fail your trust.
-May your love increase more and more, I hope.
-I hope so.
-Mother Bala.
-May it be blessed, son.
Thank you, Mother Bala.
-May your happiness last forever, if Allah permits.
-if Allah permits.
Come.
My mother gave me this necklace.
I hope you give it to
your daughter-in-law.
It's an honor for me.
-Brother.
-May Allah bless it, brother.
-Thank you.
-May it be well and blessed.
-Aameen.
Congratulations, Osman Bey.
You've seen your son get married.
May your wedding bring good luck...
...to both of the beylics.
Osman Bey, Gunduz Bey...
if Allah permits this marriage will be enough...
...to provide the unity that you desire.
If Allah permits.
Thank you. Thank you.
Not only two Kayi beylics...
...but, if Allah permits, all the beylics
will be united with us as well.
If Allah permits.
It's time now.
I've heard...
...that you are the most
powerful tradesmen of Kayi.
Yes, that's right.
We have control not only in this
market but also all the markets.
Osman made you rich.
Who are you?
I told you this while inviting you to
the wedding. No gifts will be accepted...
...from the tribe beys.
The only thing to be accepted...
...is loyalty for the fight.
We don't pledge loyalty to the one
who leaves us alone with Crusaders...
...but the one who defeated Crusaders!
-Thank you, my Bey.
-Thank you.
Not to rot off but to have
conquests one after another
..we stand beside you, Osman Bey!
Thank you. Thank you.
We don't worship the gold.
We are loyal to you, Osman Bey.
-Thank you, my Bey.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
-Thank you, my Bey.
-Sure thing.
Glorious Beys of Turks! I thank you all!
The lands beyond our dreams will be ours...
...with the conquest fire in our hearts'
And it'll be a state under whose
shadow the oppressed feel at ease forever!
My Beys! My alps! My sisters!
This state will be worth...
...all the sufferings we endured.
-if Allah permits
-Long live Osman Bey!
Long live Osman Bey! Long live
Osman Bey! Long live Osman Bey!
He's intimidating us.
I'll burn all the mountains down on him!
Long live Osman Bey! Long live
Osman Bey! Long live Osman Bey!
Burn the market. Nobody will see the morning.
May I come in, Holofira?
Sure. Come in.
What's the hurry, Alaaddin?
Gonca... We'll take Gonca away, Holofira.
The tradition of Oghuz has been served.
Thank you for being with
us on this happy day of ours.
Thank you!
May our family prosper with more children!
Draw your swords and hit the shields!
Come on, alps!
What did Orhan Bey do?
He set a big table for a wedding.
Come on!
He did many things to make Elcim Hatun happy!
He sacrificed sheep and rams.
Did he hurt anyone? Did he say evil words?
He didn't hurt anyone. He didn't say evil words.
He married Elcim Hatun!
Then, may Allah make them happy!
Aameen!
Holofira, are you alright?
-Let's go.
-Alright.
-Do I have permission, my Shahzade?
-Come in, Dogan.
My Shahzade, Alaaddin Bey
is leaving the tribe with a hatun.
What are you up to, Alaaddin?
Prepare the horses, Dogan. We're following them.
I hope you aren't doing
what is in my mind, Alaaddin.
Otherwise, nobody can save you from me.
As Kayi's children...
...we did our duty.
We united two Kayi tribes.
May our union and strength...
..last long, if Allah permits.
-I hope so.
Malhun..
I know, nothing is more
important than finding the cure.
But... roads are too dangerous.
I cannot let you go there alone.
People need you here, my
Osman. The frontiers are in danger.
Besides, our enemies will
take advantage of your absence.
Don't worry. I will heal and
come back with Allah's consent.
You will heal, you
will... I know, but..
Only our children will know this.
You will leave in disguise.
Whatever makes you feel relieved.
Stay here.
Holofira Hatun. What are you doing here?
I am leaving, Gokmen Alp.
And before I go, I want to say goodbye to Gonca.
No. Yakup Bey ordered us. I cannot let you in.
-Then... give this to her, alright?
-Alright.
What are you doing, Hatun?
My Gonca! -Alaeddin!
-I arrived my rose!
I arrived, my Gonca. I will save you. -Holofira.
Are you alright? -I am.
But if Alps hear this, they will kill you Alaeddin.
We will have left until they wake up, don't worry.
Come on Holofira. Doesn't it open?
-I will open it,I am trying.
Alaeddin... My father...
No. Don't worry.
We will find a way. We
will tire them with our love.
Come on. Come on, let's leave.
Walk! -Alaeddin!
Stand back.
-I knew you would do something stupid.
If someone ever tries to abduct
my Hatun, I will surely kill him!
You should not have done this.
I will cut your tongue off, Ahmet!
Whose Hatun is she, huh? Whose Hatun?
Is it in manhood to set your sights
on a woman who loves someone else?
Come at me... Come.
Alaeddin! Alaeddin, stop!
Stand back, Gonca.
Fight with me like a man, Ahmet.
-Like a man, huh?
Come.
Alaeddin!
Come at me.
Come. Come.
Did you call her your Hatun?
Stand up! Stand up!
She is the one I love..
Stand up! -Alaeddin!
Alaeddin
Alaeddin! -Gonca, stop!
-Alaeddin enough!
Enough! You are going to kill him! Stop!
If I had time, I would beat
you after waking you up.
But I don't have much time.
You are a lucky man, Ahmet.
Come on, walk. -Hurry.
Come on, hurry! This way! Walk!
Mother..
May Allah protect you.
My Orhan..
I am entrusting you to
Allah first, then to each other.
Don't worry about us, mother.
My angel daughter...
May Allah be with you.
Go and come back quickly, mother.
-May my Allah protect you.
Don't worry about us. Our children
are entrusted to me, Malhun.
I know.
Come on, my children.
Samil! -My Bey.
Now you will take Malhun Hatun...
..to the HatunAna healing place.
I trust you and our Alps.
I will protect your trust at
the cost of my life, my Bey.
Thank you
-My Osman...
-Malhun..
Now..
...I won't be with you on
the way. You will be alone.
But this will protect you.
Thank you, my Osman.
May my Allah protect you.
-You too.
You too. -Come on.
Come on.
You will pay for this, Alaeddin.
I will kill you.
Get the horses ready Dogan.
They kidnapped Gonca.
I'm talking to you, Dogan. Come on.
My Shahzade.
-Don't be in such a hurry.
-What are you doing here?
I'm in a hurry, move.
If that's the case, then I'll
send you to your hell quickly.
Candar, Germiyan, Kayi.
Each one of them wants to
enlarge their hunting ground.
All three of them tasted the blood.
While they are tearing each other apart,
Olcaytu will have their hunting grounds.
Osman. They are getting ready to leave.
Are we going to let them go
knowing that they will plot against us.
Alaeddin has not come yet.
Alaeddin will do what needs to be done.
Don't worry, he'll get back safe and sound.
I hope so. And then?
-They will eventually find out.
-Let it happen, Bala.
We will not be able to stop the enemy then,
but my son will be happy.
We are rejoicing as we did yesterday.
There's nothing to say about it.
They all start their own families.
That's right. That's right.
And Beys who took an oath for us...
...will form a wall for us in
between Candar and Germiyans.
We will need to be prepared for anything.
Let's see them off.
-Very well.
-May I come in, my Bey? - Come on in, Aykurt.
My Bey, they attacked Karacahisar market.
They slaughtered all the shopkeepers.
-What about the alps?
-Alps were martyred, my Bey.
-Who did this?
-We don't know, my Bey.
My Karacahisar market was attacked.
My alps, my merchants were murdered.
Among you
there are those who want to stop
my conquests through the trade.
Whoever is involved in
this will pay for it heavily.
What are you talking about Osman Bey?
We're close to the horses, they're
right behind that cliff, come on.
Alaeddin!
Stay together, don't split up.
When the jackal smells the hunt
it does not go without tearing its meat.
You are my hunt.
Who are you, dastard?
What kind of accusation is this, Osman Bey?
I've been talking openly
since you came, Ibrahim Bey.
My accusation is clear.
Whoever is involved
-will be punished.
-Neither Yakup Bey
nor I have anything to do with
your market and your merchants.
If you try to judge us without setting up a court,
you will be the one to pay the price, not us.
I'm the Bey and state here.
If there's a mistake about the justice
I'll be the judge...
...if needed.
If I find the culprit,
I'll be the one to punish him.
Yakup Bey!
Ibrahim Bey!
Ibrahim Bey, Ibrahim Bey.
What's going on?
Ibrahim Bey.
-What's this?
-Ahmet Bey.
-What’s this?
Ahmet?
Ahmet!
Ahmet! Ahmet!
My son!
Ahmet! My son!
Ahmet, wake up! Please wake up, Ahmet!
Ahmet! Ahmet!
My son! Ahmet!
My son!
Who did this? Who?
Alaeddin Bey kidnapped Gonca Hatun.
And he killed Ahmet Bey.
What are you talking about?
Are you going to be our murderer?
You will pay for this!
Ahmet!
I don't believe that my son killed him.
And I don't buy this slander.
But Ibrahim Bey, if...
...If you're gonna swing your sword at me...
...get ready for the retaliation.
Visit turkision.com for more!